

CONTACTS

miguelgillopes@hotmail.com



in @miguelgillopes



(+351) 927 747 000

SKILLS SUMMARY

Communication Skills

Adaptability

Staff Training

Process Improvement

Strong Work Ethic

LANGUAGES

●●● Portuguese

•••• English

•••• Spanish

TECHNICAL SKILLS

PHP

SwiftUI

HTML + CSS

SQL Server and MySQL

MIGUEL LOPES

DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a communicative and proactive person offering great analytical skills with a passion for programming, design and hunger for more experience at any level.

Between breaks I am usually taking some programming courses or obtaining any source of knowledge through podcasts or movies.

Feel free to throw me some challenges.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer (Back-end)

REATIA | Jun. 2020 - present

- Web Data Extraction
- Development and execution of bots
- SSL, TLS and HTTP Analysis
- Data Analysis

Full Stack Developer

Celeuma Multimédia, Lda | Feb. 2018 - Jul. 2018

- Outdoor Publicity Management Platform
- Managed project from start to finish
- Translated requirements into polished, high-efficient design

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Polytechnic Institute of Viseu

Graduation in Informatics Engineering | Out. 2015 - Set, 2019

- Worked with various languages to launch new apps and services.
- Studied project planning, coordination.

CERTIFICATES

iOS App Development

Udemy | 2022 - present (Not yet concluded)

• Knowledge in Xcode, UIKit and SwiftUI, ARKit, CoreML and CoreData.